{"showBridgeTasks":true,"taskHeader":"Granite \u0026 Stone Tile Repair Services","categoryPerformanceTest":true,"scrollyPathPageBase":"","providedPostalCode":"","hideAllSemIcons":false,"scrolly_persistedParams":{},"addressId":null,"AdobeFlickerMgmtOn":false,"SCROLLY_FILTER_NON_REQUIRED_33367":false,"headerBranding":{"src":"/images/consumer/cobranding/HA.svg","name":"ha"},"entryPointId":0,"matchingSourceId":2,"scrollyProgressBarTest":false,"isMobile":false,"consumer":{"entityId":0},"affiliateCode":"sm_def_sto","twoPageSubmit":true,"__cache./api/resource/task/40047/?r_version=1":{"taskOid":40047,"taskName":"Tile: Natural Stone (Granite, Marble, Slate, Quartz, etc) - Repair","taskDescription":"Repair Natural Stone Tile","xmTaskDescriptor":"Granite \u0026 Stone Tile Repair Services","matchable":false,"profileable":true,"esScore":0.0,"defaultCostGuideTaskId":393,"active":true,"taskKeywords":"Tile Stone Marble Quartz ceramic","textMessagingName":"Repair Tile","rolloverLongDesc":"Repair, partially replace or extend existing tile work.","rolloverShortDesc":"Repairs or alterations to existing tile work.","sectorId":"HS","metaDescription":"Find local contractors to Repair Natural Stone Tile .  HomeAdvisor will connect you with prescreened and customer-rated contractors in your area","htmlTitle":"Granite Tile Repair \u003ccity\u003e \u003cstatecode\u003e | Stone, Marble \u0026 Quartz Tile Repair","contentDescription":null,"pwcId":74,"acceptGoal":3,"multiZip":false,"preMatchTypeId":0,"bridgeTaskOid":0,"bridgeTaskText":null,"bridgeTaskLinkText":null,"bridgeTaskLinkId":0,"bridgeTaskActive":"N","xmName":"Natural Stone Tile Repair","redirectToTaskOid":-1,"spDisplayName":"Tile: Natural Stone (Granite, Marble, Slate, Quartz, etc) - Repair","xmHeaderDescriptor":"Describe Your Stone Tile Project","urlName":"Natural-Stone-Tile-Marble-Repair","taskConsiderationId":1,"siteVisible":true,"attributeMatchable":false,"htmlTitleTloc":"\u003cspcount\u003e Best Granite Tile Repair Companies - \u003ccity\u003e \u003cstatecode\u003e | HomeAdvisor Stone Tile Repairs \u0026 Costs","searchKeywords":"Tile,Stone,Marble,Quartz,ceramic,floor,mosaic,flooring,clean,tiles,etc,Slate,Granite, countertops, bathroom, kitchen","emcCategoryOid":-12073,"locationDisplayText":"What is the location of your project?","semLocationDisplayText":"To get started, enter the location of your project","commentsPromptText":"Please provide a short description of your project","primaryQuestionSetId":371,"locationSpecific":false,"commercial":false,"viewFirstParentTask":false},"sar":true,"scrolly_customDefaults":["50001_10002","8152_10002","30001_10002","160804_10002","20001_10002","160807_10002","160805_10002","502713_10002","160810_6938","8373_67562","8374_67566"],"entityId":0,"sessionId":"1564368210609pwspr010376737CC5AE756748174EA7F763C984D.pwspr010-1","shouldShowTasks":true,"KNOWN_USER_SCROLLY_TEST_SITE_33390":"ctrl","__cache./api/resource/task/interview/40047/":{"taskOID":40047,"originalTaskOID":40047,"setID":371,"interviewType":"TASK_INTERVIEW","questions":[{"questionID":5492,"questionDisplayText":"Type of Damage","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"Which best describes the nature of the damage? (Check all that apply)","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":1689,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Cracked","answerDisplayText":"Cracked","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5501,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Scratched","answerDisplayText":"Scratched","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1383,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Chipped","answerDisplayText":"Chipped","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3658,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Loose","answerDisplayText":"Loose","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":7121,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Worn","answerDisplayText":"Worn","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1946,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Discolored/Stained","answerDisplayText":"Discolored/Stained","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2113,"answerDisplaySequence":7,"answerText":"Dull/Hazy","answerDisplayText":"Dull/Hazy","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4049,"answerDisplaySequence":8,"answerText":"Need cleaned","answerDisplayText":"Need cleaned","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4069,"answerDisplaySequence":9,"answerText":"Need polished/sealed","answerDisplayText":"Need polished/sealed","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2873,"answerDisplaySequence":10,"answerText":"Grout discoloration","answerDisplayText":"Grout discoloration","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2872,"answerDisplaySequence":11,"answerText":"Grout damaged or gone","answerDisplayText":"Grout damaged or gone","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2875,"answerDisplaySequence":12,"answerText":"Grout has mold/mildew","answerDisplayText":"Grout has mold/mildew","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2877,"answerDisplaySequence":13,"answerText":"Grout needs cleaned","answerDisplayText":"Grout needs cleaned","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2879,"answerDisplaySequence":14,"answerText":"Grout needs sealed","answerDisplayText":"Grout needs sealed","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6806,"answerDisplaySequence":15,"answerText":"Want to change grout color","answerDisplayText":"Want to change grout color","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4444,"answerDisplaySequence":16,"answerText":"Other","answerDisplayText":"Other","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":5493,"questionDisplayText":"Tile Location","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":2,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"Where is the tile located? (Check all that apply)","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":1662,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Countertop","answerDisplayText":"Countertop","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":930,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Backsplash","answerDisplayText":"Backsplash","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2528,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Floor","answerDisplayText":"Floor","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6736,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Wall","answerDisplayText":"Wall","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6022,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Stairs","answerDisplayText":"Stairs","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2471,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Fireplace","answerDisplayText":"Fireplace","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6220,"answerDisplaySequence":7,"answerText":"Swimming Pool","answerDisplayText":"Swimming Pool","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4444,"answerDisplaySequence":8,"answerText":"Other","answerDisplayText":"Other","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":5488,"questionDisplayText":"Spare Tiles","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":3,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"Do you have spare tiles left over from installation?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":90000,"questionDisplayText":"Request Stage","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Choose the appropriate status for this project:","shortQuestionText":"Project Status:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":5052,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Ready to Hire","answerDisplayText":"Ready to Hire","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4702,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","answerDisplayText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":80000,"questionDisplayText":"Desired Completion Date","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":3,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"When would you like this request to be completed?","shortQuestionText":"To be completed in:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":11149,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Timing is flexible","answerDisplayText":"Timing is flexible","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11150,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Within 1 week","answerDisplayText":"Within 1 week","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11151,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"1 - 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"1 - 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11152,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"More than 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"More than 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":30001,"questionDisplayText":"Historical Work","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":4,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Is this location a historical structure?","shortQuestionText":"Is a historical structure?","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":501504,"questionDisplayText":"Property Owner","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":5,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Are you the owner or authorized to make property changes? ","shortQuestionText":"Are you the owner or authorized to make property changes? ","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":50001,"questionDisplayText":"Covered by Insurance","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":6,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Is this request covered by an insurance claim?","shortQuestionText":"Covered by an insurance claim?","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]}],"questionElements":[{"questionID":5492,"questionDisplayText":"Type of Damage","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"Which best describes the nature of the damage? (Check all that apply)","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":1689,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Cracked","answerDisplayText":"Cracked","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5501,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Scratched","answerDisplayText":"Scratched","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1383,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Chipped","answerDisplayText":"Chipped","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3658,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Loose","answerDisplayText":"Loose","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":7121,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Worn","answerDisplayText":"Worn","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1946,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Discolored/Stained","answerDisplayText":"Discolored/Stained","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2113,"answerDisplaySequence":7,"answerText":"Dull/Hazy","answerDisplayText":"Dull/Hazy","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4049,"answerDisplaySequence":8,"answerText":"Need cleaned","answerDisplayText":"Need cleaned","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4069,"answerDisplaySequence":9,"answerText":"Need polished/sealed","answerDisplayText":"Need polished/sealed","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2873,"answerDisplaySequence":10,"answerText":"Grout discoloration","answerDisplayText":"Grout discoloration","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2872,"answerDisplaySequence":11,"answerText":"Grout damaged or gone","answerDisplayText":"Grout damaged or gone","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2875,"answerDisplaySequence":12,"answerText":"Grout has mold/mildew","answerDisplayText":"Grout has mold/mildew","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2877,"answerDisplaySequence":13,"answerText":"Grout needs cleaned","answerDisplayText":"Grout needs cleaned","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2879,"answerDisplaySequence":14,"answerText":"Grout needs sealed","answerDisplayText":"Grout needs sealed","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6806,"answerDisplaySequence":15,"answerText":"Want to change grout color","answerDisplayText":"Want to change grout color","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4444,"answerDisplaySequence":16,"answerText":"Other","answerDisplayText":"Other","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":1689,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Cracked","answerDisplayText":"Cracked","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5501,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Scratched","answerDisplayText":"Scratched","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1383,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Chipped","answerDisplayText":"Chipped","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3658,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Loose","answerDisplayText":"Loose","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":7121,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Worn","answerDisplayText":"Worn","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1946,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Discolored/Stained","answerDisplayText":"Discolored/Stained","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2113,"answerDisplaySequence":7,"answerText":"Dull/Hazy","answerDisplayText":"Dull/Hazy","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4049,"answerDisplaySequence":8,"answerText":"Need cleaned","answerDisplayText":"Need cleaned","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4069,"answerDisplaySequence":9,"answerText":"Need polished/sealed","answerDisplayText":"Need polished/sealed","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2873,"answerDisplaySequence":10,"answerText":"Grout discoloration","answerDisplayText":"Grout discoloration","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2872,"answerDisplaySequence":11,"answerText":"Grout damaged or gone","answerDisplayText":"Grout damaged or gone","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2875,"answerDisplaySequence":12,"answerText":"Grout has mold/mildew","answerDisplayText":"Grout has mold/mildew","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2877,"answerDisplaySequence":13,"answerText":"Grout needs cleaned","answerDisplayText":"Grout needs cleaned","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2879,"answerDisplaySequence":14,"answerText":"Grout needs sealed","answerDisplayText":"Grout needs sealed","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6806,"answerDisplaySequence":15,"answerText":"Want to change grout color","answerDisplayText":"Want to change grout color","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4444,"answerDisplaySequence":16,"answerText":"Other","answerDisplayText":"Other","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":5493,"questionDisplayText":"Tile Location","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":2,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"Where is the tile located? (Check all that apply)","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":1662,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Countertop","answerDisplayText":"Countertop","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":930,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Backsplash","answerDisplayText":"Backsplash","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2528,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Floor","answerDisplayText":"Floor","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6736,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Wall","answerDisplayText":"Wall","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6022,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Stairs","answerDisplayText":"Stairs","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2471,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Fireplace","answerDisplayText":"Fireplace","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6220,"answerDisplaySequence":7,"answerText":"Swimming Pool","answerDisplayText":"Swimming Pool","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4444,"answerDisplaySequence":8,"answerText":"Other","answerDisplayText":"Other","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":1662,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Countertop","answerDisplayText":"Countertop","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":930,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Backsplash","answerDisplayText":"Backsplash","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2528,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Floor","answerDisplayText":"Floor","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6736,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Wall","answerDisplayText":"Wall","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6022,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Stairs","answerDisplayText":"Stairs","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2471,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Fireplace","answerDisplayText":"Fireplace","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6220,"answerDisplaySequence":7,"answerText":"Swimming Pool","answerDisplayText":"Swimming Pool","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4444,"answerDisplaySequence":8,"answerText":"Other","answerDisplayText":"Other","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":5488,"questionDisplayText":"Spare Tiles","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":3,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"Do you have spare tiles left over from installation?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":90000,"questionDisplayText":"Request Stage","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Choose the appropriate status for this project:","shortQuestionText":"Project Status:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":5052,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Ready to Hire","answerDisplayText":"Ready to Hire","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4702,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","answerDisplayText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":5052,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Ready to Hire","answerDisplayText":"Ready to Hire","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4702,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","answerDisplayText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":80000,"questionDisplayText":"Desired Completion Date","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":3,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"When would you like this request to be completed?","shortQuestionText":"To be completed in:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":11149,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Timing is flexible","answerDisplayText":"Timing is flexible","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11150,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Within 1 week","answerDisplayText":"Within 1 week","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11151,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"1 - 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"1 - 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11152,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"More than 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"More than 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":11149,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Timing is flexible","answerDisplayText":"Timing is flexible","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11150,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Within 1 week","answerDisplayText":"Within 1 week","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11151,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"1 - 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"1 - 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11152,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"More than 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"More than 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":30001,"questionDisplayText":"Historical Work","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":4,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Is this location a historical structure?","shortQuestionText":"Is a historical structure?","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":501504,"questionDisplayText":"Property Owner","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":5,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Are you the owner or authorized to make property changes? ","shortQuestionText":"Are you the owner or authorized to make property changes? ","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":50001,"questionDisplayText":"Covered by Insurance","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":6,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Is this request covered by an insurance claim?","shortQuestionText":"Covered by an insurance claim?","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]}]},"semThreeIcons":false,"isCookielessUser":true}